-I trust you had a pleasant night?
-More than pleasant.
[BOTH GIGGLE]
[GIGGLES]
(Sheldon:)Excuse me.
I'm going to relieve myself.
(Leonard:)-How do you take your coffee?
-Black.
(Leonard:)Okeydoke.
SHELDON:
Pee for Houston. Pee for Austin.
(Sheldon(in bathroom):)Pee for the state my heart got lost in.
(Sheldon(in bathroom):)And shake twice for Texas.
[TOILET FLUSHES]
(Leonard:)Something his mother taught him.
(Sheldon:)All right.
Elizabeth, the bathroom is yours.
(Sheldon:)The seat is down and has been
sanitized for your protection.
(Elizabeth:)That's very thoughtful,
but I think I'll finish my coffee first.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
(Sheldon:)Ah, so the yogurt didn't work.
(Sheldon:)I'll fire off a critical e-mail
to the manufacturer.
(Penny:)Oh, good, you're up.
My car won't start.
(Penny:)I need a ride to work.